# **Pauline Senh**

Email: plsenh@gmail.com | Phone: 267-265-9925 | Philadelphia, PA 19148

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/plsenh | Github: https://github.com/plsenh | Website: https://plsenh.github.io/

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Developer transitioning from over 4 years of professional experience in the biotechnology field including a managerial role. Experienced in collaborating with individuals from varying backgrounds and experience levels, adapting to changes and resolving conflicts in fast-paced or high stakes environments, and managing multiple side projects simultaneously.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Bootstrap, CSS3, Express.js, Firebase, Git, GitHub, HTML5, Handlebars.js, Heroku, Java, JavaScript, jQuery, MongoDB, Node.js, MySQL

### **PROJECTS**

### TamaFit | https://github.com/plsenh/TamaFit | https://tamafitpls.herokuapp.com/

Collaborator

Blog-like website where users can log their workouts, select their avatar and view a community page.

- Developed blog functionality in association with the database, api/html routes, user authentication method, display of community stats, and functionality to change avatar in real time Add 1-2 bullets summarizing what the project accomplishes and core responsibilities.
- Built with: Bootstrap, Heroku, JawsDB, MySQL, Node.js
- npm packages: animate.css, bcrypt-nodejs, express.js, express-handlebars, express-session, passport, sequelize

## GeoTunes | https://github.com/plsenh/GeoTunes | https://plsenh.github.io/GeoTunes/

**Team Lead** 

Website that shows a desired number of top songs by country via last.fm and the choice to show lyrics or listen to a song.

- Instructors awarded project with "best use of agile methodology."
- Organized GitHub issues and ensured project requirements were met.
- Implementation of Lyrics.ovh API to empty/show lyrics in conjunction with lastFM API, user input validation.
- Built with: Ajax, CSS3, Foundation CSS, HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, LastFM API, Lyrics.ovh API, Normalize CSS

### **EXPERIENCE**

# <u>Clinical Operations Manager</u> – University of Pennsylvania – Philadelphia, PA

2018 - Present

Strategically plan resource allocations, ranging from a 3-month to a yearly projection. Serve as a deputy to the Director of Operations and coordinate with other functional managers/directors. Implement and train on new electronic systems and hire, train, and supervise junior staff.

### Key Accomplishments:

- Integrated Wordpress website with custom HTML/CSS.
- Thoroughly organized and detailed operational metrics tracking.
- Introduced process improvements to cost analysis methods for faster budget development.

Clinical Operations Lead/Specialist - University of Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, PA

2016 - 2018

Research Specialist - University of Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, PA

2015 - 2016

Clinical Research Assistant - University of Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, PA

2014 - 2015

### **EDUCATION**

**University of Pennsylvania**, Philadelphia, PA – Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Temple University, Philadelphia, PA – Bachelor of Science, Biology, Minor: Cognitive Neuroscience